<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pop on benchr</title>
    <link>https://blog.benchr.de/tags/pop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pop on benchr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.benchr.de/tags/pop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3/3 - It&#39;s all about the mapping</title>
      <link>https://blog.benchr.de/post/pop-network-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.benchr.de/post/pop-network-3/</guid>
      <description>All Parts: 1 - 2 - 3
Last week I defined the interface of the Client and its Authenticator. Together with the definition of the endpoints (first part) it is now possible to take a deeper look into the actual network request. But before doing that I need to clarify one important part: the mapping of the response. Mapping JSON (or other transport formats) is a different topic, especially in Swift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 2/3 - Defining a readable and safe interface</title>
      <link>https://blog.benchr.de/post/pop-network-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.benchr.de/post/pop-network-2/</guid>
      <description>All Parts: 1 - 2 - 3
In the first part I built the foundation for a protocol oriented network abstraction written in Swift. The main focus for the component lies on safety, code quality and a very clean API.
Safety is mostly about the rules you define on how the component can be used. In the best scenario the user can not even compile the program if the component is configured wrongly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1/3 - Writing a protocol oriented network abstraction in Swift</title>
      <link>https://blog.benchr.de/post/pop-network-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.benchr.de/post/pop-network-1/</guid>
      <description>All Parts: 1 - 2 - 3
Todays topic is very technically. So if you are not interested in programming (or especially in Swift programming), this post might not be for you.
This is the first blog post of a short series. Before starting with the structure and the implementation details, I would like to explain how that topic came up.
In summer 2014, right after the announcement of Swift, I created a YouTube Channel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>